{
    "subject": "resource/Benjamin_Franklin",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Benjamin Franklin",
    "human_readable": "The name of Benjamin Franklin is Benjamin Franklin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9395070672035217,
            "question": "What is the full name of Benjamin Franklin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8900084495544434,
            "question": "Is Benjamin Franklin known by any other names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7398321628570557,
            "question": "Was Benjamin Franklin a historical figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5842782258987427,
            "question": "Where was Benjamin Franklin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5694937705993652,
            "question": "What were some of Benjamin Franklin's interests?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.519961416721344,
            "question": "In what century did Benjamin Franklin live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.483751118183136,
            "question": "What is Benjamin Franklin most famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47568318247795105,
            "question": "What are some of Benjamin Franklin's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36918365955352783,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Benjamin Franklin's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3264601230621338,
            "question": "Did Benjamin Franklin write any books?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Benjamin Franklin is Benjamin Franklin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7021_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Benjamin Franklin's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7021_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Benjamin Franklin's accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7021_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Benjamin Franklin most famous for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7021_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7021_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe triple \"Benjamin Franklin\" has multiple attributes: scientist, inventor, and statesman. This information is present in several documents (files), confirming that the triple is correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Benjamin Franklin's various roles and achievements, confirming that his full name is indeed Benjamin Franklin."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}